toshiba-india.com 2012-09-19

# Privacy Policy

Toshiba advocates online privacy. This policy will explain the following:

  * What information do we collect online and how do we use it? 
  * Which security mechanisms does Toshiba use to secure data transfers? 
  * Who will your data be shared with? 
  * Some best practice to increase your level of security 

**What information do we collect online and how do we use it?**

Your privacy is important to us. We protect your online information in the same way we protect our customer information obtained through printed orders, feedback, and correspondence. Toshiba collects information for mailing of information only when you request for it. The more additional information you volunteer (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to customise contents and make it relevant to you as an individual. Once you register you are no longer anonymous to Toshiba and are able to take full advantage of the services we can offer you.

On some parts of the website you can order products or services, check warranty, make requests, and register to receive newsletters or marketing materials. Information collected from these pages includes name, model number, serial number and contact information. Should you decide to purchase a product from the Toshiba website, we will need additional information from you, including billing and shipping address and credit card information. This information will be stored according to local legal standards for e-business transactions.

In addition, we make and keep copies of information you submit when you send email feedback to the site, ask a technical question, or report a problem. Toshiba also occasionally asks users to complete surveys that we use for research purposes.

Toshiba´s primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with customised and relevant information when you visit the site. We do not capture personal information from this site without your knowledge or permission.

When personal information is requested, visitors are given a choice as to whether they would prefer to opt-out and not receive any mailings from Toshiba.

**Which security mechanisms does Toshiba use to secure data transfers?**

Toshiba is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online as far as reasonably possible. We use encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. In certain areas of our Website, Toshiba uses SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

**Who will your data be shared with?**

Toshiba will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.

Toshiba will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:

  * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; 
  * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Toshiba to provide a product or service to you.  

**Some best practice to increase your level of security**

**Logging On**

Before logging-on, please satisfy yourself that the equipment you will be using will not permit electronic eavesdropping or recording of your activities. When logging-on, ensure that you are not being observed (by a person or by Closed-Circuit Television).

**Logging Off**

The following advice is good practice and we recommend that these steps be performed. It is particularly important that these steps are followed if you access the Toshiba Website requiring login from a public location, or one where you do not have complete control over your computer environment - such as a LAN in your workplace, an internet café etc.

Although the Toshiba Web application will log you off after a certain period of inactivity, it is recommended that you always explicitly log-off from the service when you have finished using it. This will prevent someone else gaining access to your accounts between the time when you finish using the service and automatic log off.

When you have logged-off, some information relating to your activities may remain within your computer. Please follow the next steps to ensure that no history about your activity can be found on your computer any more.

Netscape - Click on Edit>Preferences>Advanced. From the drop down menu choose Cache and then click "Clear Memory Cache" and "Clear Disk Cache" buttons

Microsoft Internet Explorer (versions 4) - Click on View>Internet Options Choose the "General" tab and on the Temporary Internet Files portion of the screen, Click "Delete Files" button

Microsoft Internet Explorer (versions 5) - Click on Tools>Internet Options Choose the "General" tab and on the Temporary Internet Files portion of the screen, Click "Delete Files" button

Please note that Toshiba reserves the right to amend this privacy policy without notice to users
